Hello friends, today's video is going to be in a very simple
format. In today's video,
we will discuss some basic principles of investing.
Buying and selling is the
world's top most difficult investment.
Fearful odds and
reduction
in excess. I think that
companies should
subscribe
in the market. So friends,
in today's video, we will talk about those that we
need and we should do it for the long term, 5 to 10 years.
So friends, now let's know about the
company that has created this will by joining these companies. Let me
tell you friends,
theirs is the insurance sector.
Theirs is banking. The third difference is that the first priority
and first priority is
technologists. So friends,
except for the technologists, the rest of us are banking.
Friends, in today's video, we will
discuss some important things. Subscribe and subscribe. So
friends, do watch this video and
in this market collection, you will get a
good position in the long term. The
name of the company is Life Insurance Company
Development Corporation of India Limited,
Bharat Finance
Tuition and Award In Global
Investment Company. There is a joint
venture between these companies. Friends, this company
works in different world class
insurance and investment products
like protection pension.  There are
some important parameters of this savings company, let's see the
market cap of this company
Stock pieces
Subscribe 7907 The
companies ROC 600 800 Companies Allegations
Since 20065 Share of the companies
630 We know that life insurance in India is less, the
coverage is very less, if we
compare it with any developed country, then the
business point of these companies is
very mean, so these
companies which are
in the south, should definitely fight for the long term
This company was established in 2001
by ICICI Bank, this company deals in general
insurance
claim management and investment
management, friends, as we
know that the introduction will be for the first time in 201, on that the
central government has made the insurance market for
bumper-to-bumper
coverage of driver, passenger and others for 5 years,
so
due to this rule, these companies  The business of will
increase by many multiples friends as
we know that there are several lakh yoga vehicles in India, its
business is going to grow, so
in these conditions our investment should definitely be done in
this company, there is some importance, let us
see the market cap of this company, that is
phase of 31st March 20, share price
16.15 CRPB price talkies 982
top 10 companies point zero seven companies and
overseas
26.8 per cent and that accused this
21.7 per share in these companies 32.4 so
friends we should definitely invest in this company for long
term
because the business of these companies is going to
grow a lot in this
video, the name of this company which we
will see in this video is Brilliant Work
Limited, so friends Jubilant Foodworks
Limited which is
a part of Bharat Bharti Group, it is the
largest service company of India, Domino Pizza is in the portfolio of this company
Dunkin' Donuts is the
master franchisee of two international brands.
This company recently added its
homegrown brand, Hong Kitchen, which is Chinese.
I just added it in the comments below. So, friends, as we are
seeing, the pending situation in India has become
very big and all the companies have
started leaving, so this company, which is
Brain Food, will have
very good business growth. In the future, this company
's results and profits will also be
seen from a good source. So, friends, we
can take a long-term bet in this company. The
position we have to take in incomplete only during the time of market correction. The
market of this company is strong. This
topic piece is
540 Stark Ste 35.8 Company, debt-free
companies are written complaint employers 60
percent companies RO is 0.2 and skimming per
series 7.5. So, friends, we should invest in this company
for the long term
because it is
a company oriented towards our lifestyle needs. So,
definitely in the long-term bet.  We
should invest in a company. So friends, today we
know that Wilfred
's ex-girlfriend, Prof. Sanjay
Mohan, has also made a fortune in the banking sector by
investing at a small price. So
friends, we should also consider a company from this segment
whose name is Kotak Mahindra Bank. Kotak
Mahindra Bank is India's leading
private Indian banking and finance
services company, whose headquarters are
in Mumbai. Friends, as we know that
banking business is a very volatile
business, we should invest in those banks
which are conservative. Kotak
Mahindra Bank is one of the most dangerous
banks to invest in. It operates in different segments like
retail banking, treasury banking,
corporate banking,
investment banking, stock broking and financial
advisory services, asset management,
life insurance and general
insurance. So friends, there is
another reason to invest in this company because
if this company suffers losses, then it can emerge as an asset
management company and
different companies in the market like stock broking
and it can have a good financial result.
So friends, let's
look at some important aspects of this company.  The
market of the company is
383861 crores. This topic piece is 38.6 stock
piece is 4.4 Ch company debt free companies ROC is
31.09
and companies accused Spark Point 2 ending
per share is 50.22 So friends,
we should definitely invest in this company for
long term. The next company that we will discuss in this video is
Nestle India Limited. Nestle India Limited is
a good multinational company. The headquarter of this company is
in Gurgaon, Haryana.
70% of the revenue of this company goes to milk and
nutritional products. 3% is
from villages and 3% is from
prepared food and kids and 3% is from
chocolates and confectionery. So
friends, the products of this company like
Lactogen in baby milk and Maggi in noodles,
it is a brand in itself and this
company has a monopoly in this business.
So friends, we should definitely
invest in this
company for long term.  Let us see some important facts of
this company, the market price of this company is
like
Zinc words of Thirty First Smartphone,
Stock Piece 32.8, Stock PBT 1.8,
228, this company is point zero two, this
company ROC 300,
Stock Accused is 105, 2.7, St and
Turning, Share Office Companies 9.5, so
friends, if there is any correction, any
dip in the market, then the companies that we have
discussed, HDFC Life Insurance, Poorvi Boyle,
Kotak Mahindra Bank,
Jubilant Foodworks and Nestle India,
position should be made in all these companies for the long term,
so friends, how did you like this video,
if you liked the video, then
like the video and subscribe to the channel so
that you get the upcoming videos
immediately, thank you for showing.